Today is day 3 of 1 Lakh per month challenge in 100 days
I have been renovating my website
it is time for a fresh
new look and some exciting updates
I'm creating this website using html
CSS Javascript and bootstrap
after completing some work on website
I designed a killer for my social media marketing
it looks great and I think you all love it
and here is the output
Yesterday I utilised a whatsapp automation software
To send out the poster in bulk
in bulk and today
I did the same software
to share today's poster in bulk as well
all the hard work on the marketing paid off
I scored a new need today
we have scheduled a physical meeting
to discuss their project